#### Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/tatianna-watwood-6847528b (LinkedIn)

### Top Skills

Web Development
Back-End Web Development
Cascading Style Sheets (CSS)

### Certifications

CCS (Certified Coding Specialist)
CRC (Certified Risk Adjustment
Coder)

# **Tatianna Watwood**

**Data Scientist** 

Huntington Beach, California

## Summary

Full stack web developer skilled in creating web applications using front and backend technologies and multiple languagues. Other relevant skills include Public Speaking, Microsoft Powerpoint Presentations, and leadership capabilities. Strong engineering professional with a Bachelor of Science (B.S.) focused in Applied Mathematics from California State University, Long Beach.

You can find some of my current projects I have worked on at https://tatiannad.github.io/

## Experience

Freelance

Full Stack Developer/Data Analyst June 2017 - Present (2 years 10 months) Remote

Write well designed, testable, efficient code by using best software development practices

Create website layout/user interface by using standard HTML/CSS practices Integrate data from various back-end services and databases Gather and refine specifications and requirements based on technical needs

Stay plugged into emerging technologies/industry trends and apply them into operations and activities

Cooperate with web designers to match visual design intent

MemorialCare
Risk Adjustment Coder/Analyst

February 2019 - July 2019 (6 months)

Fountain Valley, CA

**Abstracting Codes** 

Auditing physician performance

**Process Improvement** 

Provider Feedback

agilon health

Risk Adjustment Coder/Analyst

December 2016 - February 2019 (2 years 3 months)

Remote

Coding and Abstracting HCC records (AHA/Progress forms)

Capturing quality codes

**Data Validation** 

**Process Improvement** 

Auditing

Staying in compliance with CMS guidelines

**Nearterm Corporation** 

Medical Coder (Contract)

November 2015 - April 2017 (1 year 6 months)

Remote

Remote OP (ED, SDS, Ancillary) charts

Knowledge of APC

Knowledge of ICD 10CM/PCS

Responsible for applying accurate codes to various types of patient's records

Maintain 95-97 accuracy and percent productive quality

accuracy and issues

## Education

University of California, Irvine

The Coding Bootcamp, Full stack web development · (2017)

California State University-Long Beach

Bachelor of Science (B.S.), Applied Mathematics · (2013 - 2015)

California State University-Long Beach

Bachelor of Science (B.S.), Mathematical Economics · (2013 - 2015)

Long Beach City College

· (2010 - 2013)